打扰一下 真是不好意思
Excuse me, I'm so sorry.
我从不跟名人打招呼
I never do this for celebrities.
但你是不是新视野不动产广告
But are you by any chance the foxy mom
里面那位性感迷人的辣妈呀
on the New Horizon realty ad.
我会后悔做这个吗
Am I gonna regret doing that?
拍万宝路广告那个人后悔过吗
Did the marlboro man have any regrets?
这个广告太完美了
This ad is perfect.
看 我不只是在卖房子
See, I'm not just selling houses,
我还在宣传我自己
I'm selling myself,
最让我引以为傲的就是我的家庭
and the best part about me is my family.
还有我的牙齿
And my teeth.
而这些 都将呈现在这则广告上
And both...are on display in this ad.
"您满意 我满足"
"I can't be satisfied until you're satisfied"?
你即将在巴士候车亭看见
Coming soon to a bus bench near you,
更别说我们的小货车了
not to mention our minivan.
所以你是来真的咯
So that's really happening?
等等 我们的小货车怎么了
Wait. What's happening to our minivan?
要被这个坏家伙贴身黏上
Having this bad boy shrink-wrapped on it.
-漂亮 -是啊
- Classy. - Yep.
现在就算你妈开车瞎晃 也能干点正事了
Now all that driving around your mom does will serve a purpose.
早上好 亲人们
Good morning, family.
在这个美好的日子里 你们过得怎么样
How are you all doing on this beautiful day?
很好 这是怎么回事
Okay. What's this?
海莉的高考成绩可以在网上查询了
Haley's S.A.T. scores are available online.
我恨你
I hate you.
今天可是个大日子
Oh! ! Today's the big day.
我们来看看 她考的怎么样
Let's take a look, see how she did.
我们真的要现在就看么
Do we really have to look at them now?
不用担心
Don't worry.
我们不期望会有奇迹发生
We're not expecting any miracles.
谢谢
Thank you.
这些是海莉的分数吗 你确定
Are those Haley's scores? Are you sure?
为什么 很低么
Why? Are they bad?
不 它们不低
No, they're not bad.
那很高吗
Are they good?
也不 中等水平
No, they're average.
亲爱的 我们成功了
Sweetie, we did it.
我们的孩子是中等
Our baby's average.
中等万岁
Medium five!
这只是一个偶然
This is just a fluke.
她还可以再考一次
She can take them again.
是的 她或许还能考得更好
Yeah, and she'll probably do even better.
到时候你就可以有
You are gonna have your choice
好几个很好的大学可供选择了
of some pretty good colleges when the time comes.
前提是我得去大学
If I go to college.
什么
What?
我最近一直在想这个
I've been thinking about it lately,
我或许 不会去
and I might...not.
待会见
Later!
虽然成绩出乎意料的不错
Well, we took the scenic route,
但烂泥终究扶不上墙
but we ended up in the same place.
从津巴布韦到阿尔及利亚
From Zimbabwe to Algeria
来吧 让我听到你的声音
Come on, let me hear ya
就是这些国家了 就是这些国家了
These are the countries, these are the countries
小卡最近成了富兰克林中学的
Cam recently became Franklin middle school's
加油 富兰克林
Go, Franklin!
我自告奋勇为他们的春季音乐会效力
I was volunteering for their spring musical festival
突然莫名其妙的病了
suddenly and mysteriously became ill.
对不起
Oh, sorry.
这可能是他们的福分
It may have been a blessing.
他们的演出没什么重点
Their show lacked focus.
是我为它制定了一个主题
I gave it a theme --
"环球音乐之旅"
"A musical trip around the world."
是的 瞧 他的重点就是
Yeah, see, he focused it
把它跟世界联系起来
by making it about the world.
你不喜欢这个
You don't like it.
不 小卡 我喜欢
No -- Cam. I do.
你认为那些孩子们
Do you -- do you think that the kids, though,
今晚就能学会吗
are gonna be able to learn it by tonight?
我是说 或许你可以着重于
I mean, maybe you should stick
他们之前排练好的节目
with something that they already know.
我就知道会这样
I knew this would happen.
为什么你总是要浇熄我炙热的梦想呢
Why do you have to throw a wet blanket on my dreams?
-我没有 -你一直都这样
- I do not. - You do it all the time.
你知道我是以什么告终的么 梦遗
And you know what I end up with? Wet dreams.
这词一脱口而出我就后悔了 不要管它
I heard it as soon as I said it. Just leave it alone.
好的 小卡 只不过有时候
All right, well, Cam, it's just that sometimes
你有点小小的过分热情了
you can be a little, you know, overenthusiastic.
我想让它变成世界上最好的演出
Is it really that big of a deal
这真有那么大的关系么
that I want this to be the best show in the world?
该说的我都说了
Well, as long as you heard me.
站在我这一边 不要这么吹毛求疵
Be in my corner. Don't be so critical.
你真的是这么看我的么
We-- is that really how you see me?
有时候我确实是这么看你的 米奇尔
Sometimes, yeah, I do, Mitchell.
小卡 如果这是真的 我很抱歉
Cam, well, if -- if that's true, then I'm -- I'm sorry.
不 好的 从现在开始
No, you know, okay, from now on,
我百分百站在你那边
I am in your corner 100%.
这首歌一定会艳惊四座
Yeah, that song is gonna knock everyone out.
我不知道 不过
Well, I don't know, but
等你看了我准备的舞蹈再说吧
wait till you see the dance I have prepared.
舞蹈 舞蹈
A dance? A dance!
再来一些吐司么 曼尼
More toast, Manny?
你为什么不给我打电话呢 艾玛
Why won't you call me, Emma?
再来一些吐司么 艾玛
More toast, Emma?
你有必要什么时候都来掺一脚么
Do you have to be on all the time?
好的 对不起 谁是艾玛
Okay, I'm sorry. Who is this Emma?
她是我今晚表演的同伴
She's in the show with me tonight.
我正在考虑追她
I'm thinking of taking a run at her.
你不该"追"女生
You don't "Take a run" at a woman.
你得取悦她 让她觉得她是特别的
You woo her. You make her feel special.
亲爱的 看看这个
Hey, hon, take a look at this.
这是我屁屁的照片
It's a picture of my butt.
你把她拿下之后
And then when you get her,
你就可以随心所欲了
you can tell her whatever you want.
你为什么要这么做
Why do you do this?
只要我哥哥唐尼一打电话来
I programmed it so my butt pops up
我的屁屁就会跳出来
when my brother donnie calls.
借用屁屁来鄙视我哥 只用聪明人才会的招数呀
It's a clever way of saying my brother's an ass.
是吗
Is it?
他来了 淡定淡定
That's him. Compose yourselves.
忘了我给你们看过这张照片
Forget I showed you this picture.
我尽力
I'm trying.
你过得咋样 婊子养的傻儿子
How you doing, you dumb son of a bitch?
你个老不死的 看起来你又胖了几磅
You old mick. Looks like you've put on a few pounds.
彼此彼此
Oh, you too.
你是不是连你头发都给吃了
What, are you eating your hair?
歌洛莉亚
Oh, Gloria. Oh.
你怎么还在这儿
What are you still doing here?
拿绿卡的办法多了 肯定还有更容易的
There's got to be an easier way to get a green card.
唐尼伯伯
Hey, uncle Donnie,
你今晚会来我的校园音乐会么
are you coming to my school concert tonight?
-这个嘛 -最多就一个小时
- Well... - It's an hour, tops.
我肯定去
...wouldn't miss it.
我找不到我的电话了
Hey, you know, I think I misplaced my phone.
你能用你的手机打我的吗
Could you call me on yours?
我手机在包的最底下
My phone's at the bottom of my bag.
为什么不用你家里的电话打呢
Why don't you use your home phone?
得了吧 这很简单
Oh, come on. It's simple.
你要干嘛
What are you doing?
我要电话
I want the phone.
你放手怎么样
How about you let go, you --
把电话给我 唐尼
Give me the phone, Donnie!
你还以为你能放倒我么
You still think you can take me?!
怎么了 你就这种水平吗
What? Is this all you got, huh?
我要你的嘴尝尝老子拳头的滋味
I'm gonna wash your mouth out with fist.
我真不明白这种兄弟情 艾玛
I don't understand this relationship, Emma.
艾玛
Hey, Emma.
做这场表演 就像是
Doing this show, it feels like
我们成为了一个小家庭 是吧
we've become like a little family, huh?
你是说你就像是我兄弟一样么
You mean like you're my brother?
不不 不是
No. N-no, I don't.
不
Oh, no!
他们回来了 恐龙武器
They're back -- dinosaur arms!
现在可不是个好时候 卢克
This isn't a good time, Luke.
这可真是搞笑
That is hilarious.
半人半恐龙
Half boy, half t-rex.
身处人兽两界之间
One foot in both worlds,
而为两界所不容
Wanted by neither.
卢克 你把衣服撑大的方法真不错
Luke, that's a great way to stretch out a shirt.
好了好了 休息结束了 大家伙儿
Okay, okay! Break's over, everyone!
让我们从头再来一遍
Let's take it from the top.
听着 因为演出时间是20分钟
Listen, we're running 20 minutes long,
所以我们要去掉宝莱坞部分继续演
So we're gonna go ahead and cut the Bollywood number.
我能离开了吗 我足球练习迟到了
Can I go? I'm late for soccer practice.
你知道还有谁错过了足球练习吗 德尔罗伊
You know who else missed soccer practice, Delroy?
《吉屋出租》的演员们 而他们赢得了东尼奖
The cast of "Rent." And now they have a Tony.
我们也有一位东尼
We have a Tony.
你太搞笑了
You are so funny.
不会吧
Seriously?
喂
Hello?
甜心 他们把车开来了吗
Hey, honey. Did they drop the van off yet?
刚刚开来
Yeah, a little while ago.
看起来怎么样
How's it look?
信不信由你
Uh, well, believe it or not,
我忍住了不去看
I have resisted the temptation to look.
海莉的事情搞得我有点头大
This whole Haley thing has got me a little preoccupied.
我们正要去吃饭
We're on our way out to lunch right now.
关于那个我有个看法
About that, I've been thinking.
大学还早着呢
College is still a ways away.
我觉得应该让海莉自己考虑
I say we leave Haley alone.
我们越是给她压力 她越是反抗
The more we push, the more she'll push back.
我就是要给她压力
I'm gonna push.
我坚决支持
And I support that.
也只有老爹能把我们的车搞得更丑
Only dad can make our minivan even lamer.
不好意思 你在搞啥
Excuse me. What are you doing?
我要把这车开到水库里面去
I'm driving this thing to the reservoir.
我叫你跳车 你就跳
Just jump when I say jump.
亲爱的 坐过去
Honey, slide over.
靠这种蹩脚广告怎么能卖出房子
How is this stupid ad supposed to sell houses anyway?
你也听你爸说过
You heard your father.
他不只是在卖房子
He's not just selling houses...
他是在宣传我们
He's selling us.
我的朋友会怎么想
What are my friends gonna think?
他们会想
They are gonna think
你在帮你老爸捞钱
that you're helping your father put food on the table.
- 椅子坏了吗 -算是吧
- Ay, is the chair broken? - Almost.
我那个贪便宜吃白食的哥哥
That cheap, freeloading brother of mine
老是对我的上好苏格兰威士忌恋恋不忘
can't keep his hands off my good Scotch,
你看 我把威士忌放那里
So, you see, I placed that Scotch there.
只要我哥哥一屁股坐上面 椅子就会立马散架
My brother sits in this chair, goes out from under him --
啪嗒 杰作呀
Bam! -- Masterpiece.
你就让你兄弟摔倒 把酒洒了吗
So you make your brother fall and spill his drink?
我也不想让酒跟着遭殃 但计划就是这样
Well, I don't want to jinx it, but that's the plan.
你们俩怎么都那么小气
Why are you both so mean?
我长大的地方 兄弟互相尊敬
Where I come from, brothers respect each other.
所以说哥伦比亚才是"世外桃源"
That's why Colombia is such a peaceful utopia.
两位小姐 你们好
Hello, ladies.
嘿 衣服不错
Hey, nice shirt.
你去买衣服的地方有卖男人衣服吗
Do they sell men's clothes where you got that?
有意思 因为妇女一向地位低下
That's funny because women are so inferior.
你真没品位
You got no taste.
我专门为了梅莱尼的洗礼买的
I bought this for Melanie's baptism.
梅莱尼是谁
Who's Melanie?
迈克的孩子 我的孙女
Michael's kid, my granddaughter.
哦 忘了跟艾琳说我平安抵达了
Oh, I forgot to tell Irene I landed safely.
喂
Hello?
你怎么能不知道
How could you not know
你自己的兄弟有孙女了
that your own brother had a granddaughter?
我好像知道
I probably knew.
你怎么能连家人的事情都不记得了
How can you forget when he's family?
我有29个堂兄弟姐妹 我能一一道来
I have 29 cousins, and I know them all --
罗莎·玛琳娜 歌洛莉亚·玛琳娜
Rosa Marina, Gloria Maria,
-维罗妮卡·玛琳娜 何塞·维森特 -够了够了
- Veronica Maria, Jose Vicente - Okay, okay, okay.
你想说什么
What's your point?
你破坏椅子 你跟他打架
You do the chair, you do the fighting,
但是你们就是不了解对方
But you don't know each other.
悲剧啊
It's sad.
听着 虽然我跟我哥哥的交流方式
Look, I may not talk to my brother
与你和你的姐妹的不一样
the way you talk to your sisters,
但是相信我 我们有我们的友爱方式
But believe me, we're close in our own way.
你上次见他是什么时候
When was the last time that you saw him?
我们见面没那么容易 因为他住在
Well, that's not easy, 'cause he lives up...
看吧 我想说水牛城来着
See, I want to say Buffalo.
我想说的是
All I'm saying
多接受点教育没什么不好的
is that there's no downside to more education.
我早就知道你开车带我出来另有所图
I knew this car ride was a trap.
看见没有
See that?
从这句话我就知道你有多聪明
That right there shows me just how smart you are.
没搞错吧 又来了
Really? Again?
怎么回事
What is going on?
就是那个蹩脚广告
It's the stupid ad.
那些人也跑到我这边按喇叭
They're honking on my side, too.
没错 广告上就是我们
Yes, we're the people in the ad.
你们好
Yeah. Hi.
大学还有另外一大好处
Another great thing about college
完全的自由
complete independence.
我外面住公寓一样自由
I'd have that in an apartment.
不 你要租公寓 必须得有工作
No, because to have an apartment, you would need a job.
知道在学校你的工作是什么吗
You want to know what your job is in college?
上上课啦 做做作业啦
It's a little bit of class and homework.
交许许多多的朋友啊
And it's a whole lot of new friends.
各种各样的体验呀
And experiences.
男孩觉得你可爱 而你确实处于可爱的青春年少
And the boys think you're cute and you are cute,
相信我 青春转瞬即逝
And, oh, trust me, that doesn't last forever.
打电话就是了
Call the number!
好极了
All right!
准备好输球了吗
You in the mood to lose?
你哥我还没输过球呢
First time for everything.
你开球
You break.
工作怎么样
So, how's work?
不用着急 有钱哥 我不是来借钱的
Don't worry, moneybags. I'm not here for a loan.
开得好
Nice break.
好啦 全色球归你
All right, you're solids,
不过估计你得半天才能动杆子了
which you won't be able to eat in a few years.
好好
Right, right.
说真的 你最近过得如何
Seriously, though, how are things going with you?
好得很
Swell.
我现在就在台球桌上教训一个胖子
I'm beating a fat guy at pool right now.
唐尼 我试图和你交谈呢
Donnie, I'm trying to talk to you.
为什么
Why?
为什么 因为普通人都这样做吧
Why? 'cause that's what people do.
谈天说地 比如说他们的生活
Talk about things, like their lives.
艾琳原来是下我套来着
Oh, Irene opened her big trap.
听着 我很好
Look, I'm fine.
我又不是要死掉了
It's not like I'm gonna die.
什么
What?
医生发现得早
Yeah, they caught it early.
化疗过后 现在好了
I took the treatment. I'm clear for now.
快点 该你了
Come on. It's your shot.
诊断出啥了
Caught what early?
唐尼 你是不是说
Donnie, are you talking about...
癌症
cancer?
没什么好避讳的 我知道我得癌症了
You don't have to whisper. I know I got it.
我的前列腺检查是医生做的
You just get your prostate checked -- by a doctor,
又不是在网上认识的人
not some guy you met on the internet.
我不敢相信你居然瞒着我
I can't believe you didn't tell me this.
这又没什么大不了的
Because it's not a big deal.
听着 这件事就咋俩知道
Now, listen. It's just between us.
天啊
Oh, god.
艾琳 我怎么知道你的破眼镜在哪
Irene, how the hell do I know where your glasses are?
还有飞盘高尔夫啦
And there's frisbee golf,
你还可以用自助餐厅的大盘子当雪橇滑雪
And -- and you go snow-sledding on cafeteria trays.
你和室友还可以一起养条狗
Oh, and you all get a dog together.
我不知道暑假的时候是谁照顾它的
I don't really know who takes care of the dog during the summer,
反正你回去的时候它肯定在
but he's there when you get back.
有完没完 或许你应该回去念大学
Geez, maybe you should just go back to college.
亲爱的 如果时光能倒流我真的什么都愿意
Oh, honey, do you know what I would give to go back?
那一刻你所有的生活都在你跟前 由你随心所欲
It's this moment when your whole life is in front of you,
太神奇了
and it's a magical time.
你绝对不会想错过的
You don't want to miss that,
因为光阴一去不复返
Because when it's gone, it's gone.
别烦 别烦
Yeah, yeah.
快点 艾丽克斯 车要开了
Come on, Alex. Bus is leaving.
老爸 你手机震个不停
Dad, your phone's been buzzing like crazy.
我滴个乖乖
Sweet lorna doone!
十九个未接来电
19 missed calls?
到底是谁...
I wonder who's --
菲尔·邓菲
Phil Dunphy.
你看过那个广告啊
You saw the ad?
太好了
Great.
你想找什么样的
Do you know what you're looking for?
小的那个吗
The little one?
我明白你说的是哪个
I think I know which one you're talking about.
要是你感兴趣的话
Um, if you're interested,
我有个品质尚佳的老款
I also have an older model with a lot of character.
什么
What?
我觉得地毯和窗帘很配啊
I think the carpet matches the drapes.
我有段时间没看过了
I haven't checked in a while.
两个都想要啊
Both of them?
天啊
Wow.
要是你打算要一个的话 我还能理解
Well, I guess that makes sense if you're planning to flip one.
这样吧 我等会回你好吧
Listen, um, why don't I call you back?
我们约个时间
We'll set up an appointment.
我会抓紧时间把它们都清洗干净
It'll give me a chance to give them both a good scrubbing.
行
All right.
非常感谢
Thanks a lot.
再见
Bye-bye.
不错吧
How about that, huh?
你看这些电话都是问那个广告的
You think all these calls are about the ad?
是啊
Yeah.
我朋友妮可刚把咱们家小货车的照片发给我
My friend Nicole just sent me a picture of the van.
我觉得你老妈要
I guess I'll be seeing you wednesdays
气得跟我离婚了
and every other weekend.
你好
Hello?
这样的 听上去你很生气
Okay, um, you sound very angry,
这我完全理解
which is completely understandable.
我没生气
I'm not angry.
我只是坐在这里 回想我的大学生涯
I'm just sitting here thinking about college
回忆曾经的青春年少
and how life has passed me by.
谢天谢地 我们表演会上见
Oh, thank god. I'll see you at the show.
爱你 拜拜 快走
Love you. Bye. We got to go.
音乐到达高潮的时候
And as the music swells,
我们举起手里的字母
we reveal our letters
拼成"我们爱世界"
spelling "We love the world."
很好很强大
Powerful stuff.
然后宏伟的富兰克林中学的标志
And then the majestic Franklin middle school insignia
就会缓缓就位
will drop into position
不过前提是鲁本能把标志画完
if Reuben ever finishes painting it.
这不是艺术殿堂 鲁本
It's not the sistine chapel, Reuben.
惊喜吧
Surprise! Hey!
鼎力支持的男友顺路带点心给你吃啦
Your supportive boyfriend dropped by to bring you a snack.
梨梨 小布里和肉肉
P.B. And J.
梨子 布里干酪配火腿 我最爱啊
Pear, brie, and jambon. My favorite!
同志们 休息五分钟
Okay, people, let's take five.
就五分钟哦
A true five.
曼尼 怎么样啊
Hey, Manny. How's it going?
好 很好 好得不能再好了
Good, great, couldn't be better.
我们能不能...
Can we, uh...
行 当然 没问题
Yes, we can, uh -- all right.
怎么了
What's up?
听着 你需要跟小卡谈谈
Okay, you got to talk to Cam.
他要把我们逼疯了
He's driving us crazy.
凯文又开始咬指甲了
Kevin is biting his nails again,
鲁本一周都没有拉便便了
And Reuben hasn't had a bowel movement in a week.
别笑 猫王就是被逼死的
Don't laugh. That's how Elvis died.
好吧 曼尼
All right, um, Manny,
我...我不能参与进去的
I-I can't get involved.
但 好吧 要是你想反映情况
But, all right, if you have to say something,
就去告诉犀利哥 说他做过头了
just tell Bob Fussy that he's overdoing it
告诉他你们想回到原来那样
and you want to go back to your old stuff.
好了 休息结束 同志们
Okay, break's over, people!
我们再来次法国大革命那一段
I want to do the french revolution number again.
我们把断头台拿上来
Let's bring out the guillotine.
这次用点心了
Carefully this time.
不要 不要 不要了
No, no, no.
什么
Excuse me?
我们不想做这个新玩意
We don't want to do the new stuff.
我们不想继续排练
We want to stop rehearsing
想用原来的方式演绎 犀利哥
and go back to the old way, Bob Fussy.
我 我不知道那词哪来的
I-I don't know where this is coming from.
你们都这么认为吗
You all feel this way?
是的 是的 是的 是的
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
行了 我不知道
Well, I had no idea.
我不知道我周围是一群懒人
I had no idea I was surrounded by a bunch of quitters.
要不是我把音乐剧大师
This production was a joke
伯恩斯坦和桑坦介绍给孩子们
until I introduced these children
这个破音乐剧
to the musical-theater greats --
还只是个大笑柄
Bernstein, Sondheim.
几年后 有个别孩子就会谈论
Years from now, some of these kids
当初我如何将他们桑坦化的
will still be talking about the way I sondheim-ized them.
我觉得那样说不太好...好吧
Ooh, I'm don't think that's a good way of saying -- okay.
你想用原来的方式吗
You want to do it the old way
用这首没新意老歌和死气沉沉的编舞
with the same tired songs, the same drab choreography,
然后得到父母敷衍的欢呼吗
the same tepid applause from mom and dad?
你们真的想吗 回答我
Is that what you want? Just say the word.
我们就是那样想的 是的 是的
That's what we want. Yes. Yes.
行了 伙计们 很遗憾
Well, too bad, people!
我说了算 重来
We're doing it my way! From the top!
这是封闭式彩排 闪开
This is a closed rehearsal. March.
亲爱的 你在外面干什么
Hi, honey. What are you doing out here?
等你啊 因为我爱你
Oh, just waiting for you 'cause I love you.
海莉 从这边下来
Haley, come out this side.
为什么
Why?
因为很好玩啊 试试
'Cause it's fun. Try it.
滑动门 移动坐垫
Yeah, the doors slide, the seats slide.
这车无所不能啊
What can't the sienna do?
真搞笑
That was fun.
是吗 去看表演吧
Right? Let's go see a show!
亲爱的 我们应该把门关上
Sweetie, we need to close the door.
是的 用钥匙就行
Yeah, with the key.
我想看看走多远
I like to see how far I can get from the car
还能控制这车
and still make it work.
听着 亲爱的 亲爱的
Listen, honey, honey.
-怎么 -我要问你些事
- Yeah? - Let me ask you something.
你要实话实说
Okay, I need you to be really honest with me.
行啊 你可...行
Yeah, you ca-- yes.
我是不是人老珠黄了
Are my best years behind me?
说什么啊
What?
当然不是
No.
秘诀就是向前看
The trick is to keep looking forward.
走吧
Here we go.
真的吗
Really?
是的是的 千真万确
Yes, yes, for sure.
好些没
You feel good?
是啊 我...
Yeah, I...
大家好 欢迎各位
Hello, and welcome, everyone.
以及迟到的人们
And latecomers.
希望大家能喜欢今晚的表演
I hope you enjoy the show tonight.
你们一定赞同这个舞台已经多年
I think you will agree it has a certain flair
没有高水准高质量的表演了吧
that has been lacking from this stage in years past.
所以 请容许我邀您坐稳当 放轻松
So, please, I invite you to sit back, relax,
尽情享受这趟世界音乐旅程吧
and enjoy this musical trip around the world!
天呐
Wow.
在美国长大是很不错
Growing up in America sure is great,
但我还想对世界了解的更多
but I wish I knew more about the world.
我也是
Me too.
我有个主意
I think I've got an idea.
待会见 朋友
See you later, friend.
你去哪里
Where are you going?
去见见世界
To see the world!
中国看上去很有趣
China looks interesting.
我就在这里着陆吧
I think I'll land here.
放他下来
Bring him down!
继续 继续演
Just go with it. Go with it.
天啊 搞什么啊
Oh. Hey. Come on.
天啊 搞什么呀
Geez, come on,
杰 你在剧院里呢
Jay. You're in the theater.
看看你夹克的口袋
Try your jacket pocket.
不好意思伙计们
Sorry, folks.
厉害 他用胶带把手机封死了
Nice. He taped it shut.
行了 别闹了
Okay, that's enough.
傻子啊 你也是
Ay! Stupid! You too!
别打他 他得癌症了
Don't hit him. He has cancer.
什么
What --
天啊 卢克是被卡在那儿了吗
Oh, my god, is Luke stuck up there?
菲尔
Phil?
拜托
Come on.
没错儿
Yeah.
对-- 别 哦不
Ye-- oh, no.
拜托
Come on!
中国是挺有意思的
China sure was fun.
不过看啊 那儿还有快乐的老英格兰
and look, there's merry old England.
难道看表演的人都没见过地球仪吗
Has anyone here ever seen a globe?
全速前进
Full steam ahead!
是前进
Ahead!
别管那个了 你就唱吧
Just sing.
哦 睁开被海风吹拂的眼睛
Oh, joy to salt-swept eyes
我欣喜地看见了 那美丽的英格兰
Fair England, do I see
抱歉我告诉了歌洛莉亚
Sorry about what I said to Gloria, okay?
就是一时脱口而出了
Just came out.
咱们进去吧
Let's go back inside.
-打我一下 -什么
- Hit me. - What?
你听见我说的了 打我一下
You heard me. Hit me.
我不会打你的 唐尼
I'm not gonna hit you, Donnie.
没错 这就是重点
Yeah, well, that's the whole damn point.
你一听说我病了
As soon as you heard I was sick,
你对待我的方式就不一样了
you treated me different.
我告诉你吧 那些我在家就受够了
Let me tell you, I get enough of that at home.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我就是有点儿替你难过 行吗
I feel a little bad for you, okay?
我知道我们不常说这些 可是...
I know we don't say this much, but, uh...
我是关心你的 你知道吗
I care for you, you know?
你以为我不知道这点屁事儿吗
Do you think I don't know that crap?
自从我八岁你十岁那年
I have known you cared about me
那个蠢货乔伊·可列里偷了我的自行车
since we were 8 and 10 years old
你把他的头埋进冰里之后
and that mook Joey Calieri stole my bike
我就知道你是关心我的
and you put his head in the ice.
他当时说什么来着
What was that he said again?
"我再也听不见了"
Um, "I can't hear no more."
"I can't hear no more!"
唐
oh, Don.
你的舞台装饰被弄得到处都是
Your stage is all over the place.
孩子们都累疯了
The kids are exhausted.
你就在那儿照自己的意思演
You're making all about you.
连幕间休息都没有
No intermission.
你把我们当动物了是吗
What, are we animals?
我...
I --
我会好的
I'm gonna be fine.
我有很好的医生
I got great doctors.
孩子们每天都给我打电话
The kids call me every day.
艾琳因为压力过大 还瘦了20磅呢
Irene even lost 20 pounds due to stress.
真不错
Good for you.
你答应我你会好好做个肝区检查
You promise me you'll get that liver checked out.
哎呀 根本没--
Ah, there's nothing wrong--
拜托 唐 您老就忍着点吧
Come on, Donna. Suck it up.
我们都错过我儿子的演出了
We're missing my kid's show.
你这混蛋
You son of a bitch.
来吧来吧
Come on. Come on.
"我再也听不见啦"
"I can't hear no more!"
好了好了
Okay, all right.
刚才那个是我的错
That one was my fault,
不过圣女贞德会没事儿的
But Joan of Arc's gonna be just fine.
这剧没了艾玛就没意思了
It's not gonna be much fun doing the show without Emma.
也许我们应该到此为止
Maybe we should just stop this.
别 不行 在戏剧界有句俗话叫
No. No. There is a saying in the theater world that --
"为它丧命实属不智"吗
"It's not worth dying for"?
不 是"结尾成就一切"
No, it's that "Endings make shows."
再说我们那个结尾那么好
And we've got a great ending.
所以现在赶紧出去给我充满感情地唱
Now get out there and sing your hearts out.
亲爱的你就别唱了 你对口型就行了
Oh, not you, sweetie. You just mouth the words. Okay.
小卡叔叔 我两条腿都疼了
Uncle Cam, both my legs are tingly.
卢克 我们马上就把你放下来行吗
Okay, we'll cut you down in just a second, Luke, okay?
演出得继续 要乐在其中哦
The show must go on. Have fun with it.
了解这个世界的确很有趣
Learning about the world sure was fun.
但是能够重新两脚着地 我也挺高兴的
But I'm glad to have my feet back on the ground again.
埃及土地 金字塔耸立
Oh, Egypt is a land where the pyramids stand
勤劳的犹太人 把它们全部建起
Which were built by industrious jews
风车们在荷兰的村庄 随处可见
And windmills go around in Holland town
那里的人们 都穿着木头做的鞋
Where they all wear wooden shoes
我们学了很多东西 在今天这一天
These are the things we learned today
千言万语 只剩一句
And there's one last thing we want to say
"我们爱这个词"
"We love the word"
怎么少一个字母
Where's the "L"?
应该是卢克拿着
That's luke.
把那个标志牌放低点儿
Lower the insignia.
低点儿
Lower it.
我们爱...
"We love the --"
搞什么啊
What the hell?
不 不对 不是 不 不
No, no, no. No, no.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
不 不 不 不 不
No. No, no, no. No.
太精彩了
Brava!
菲尔 你去哪儿了
Phil, where have you been?
就是呼吸点儿新鲜空气
Oh, just getting some fresh air.
-亲爱的 -呼吸完了
- Honey. - Got it.
要走了吗 嘿 看看月亮吧
Ready to go? Hey, look up at the moon.
你说这是满月呢 还是弦月呢
Would you say that's waxing or waning?
管他呢 我们能花一晚上看
Who cares? We can spend all night looking --
"我不能被满足"
"I can't be satisfied"?!
我的天啊 菲尔
My God, Phil.
这话让我看起来跟个妓女一样
That makes me look like a prostitute.
没有
No.
有 就有
Yes. Yes, it does.
其实更像个三陪
More of an escort, really.
三陪的只是出卖时间而已
You're just selling your time.
-但是妓女是-- -行了菲尔
- Whereas a prostitute just-- - Okay, Phil.
我今天一整天都开着这车跑来跑去
I have been driving around in this all day.
好吧 既然你已经生气了
Well, since you're mad already,
为什么你不到这边来
why don't you just step over here
看看这个呢
and have a look at that?
上帝啊 我的宝贝女儿
Oh, God. My baby.
我绝不再坐那辆车
I am not getting back in that car!
得了吧 亲爱的 那你怎么回家呢
Oh, how do you think you're gonna get home, honey?
无所谓 我随便跟谁回家都行
It doesn't matter! I'll go home with anyone!
这话才应该写在车上呢
That's what it should say on the van.
艾丽克斯
Alex.
真不敢相信
I can't believe we trusted you
经过上次失败的照片教训
to put this on the car
我们还敢让你把照片贴车上
after the debacle of that last picture.
妈的
Damn it.
而你-- 是谁
And that -- who was that?
可能是另一个...
Probably another...
我觉得你想说的可能是"路人甲"
I think the word you're looking for is "John."
上车
Get in the minivan.
你是想告诉我说
You mean to tell me that
的确有人打电话来要特殊服务是吗
people have actually been calling about this?
变态多得是
There are a lot of creeps out there.
那也太恶心了 她还是个孩子
That's disgusting. She's a child.
公平点儿说 大部分是打来要你服务的
Well, to be fair, most of them were for you.
那也很恶心好吗
Well, it's still sick.
你说"大部分" 是多少
What do you mean, "Most"?
我不知道 差不多有三十通电话
Well, I don't know. There were 30 calls.
二十多个都是找你的
You got 20 or 25 of them.
那他们...点名找我吗
And they...ask for me?
他们要那个金发辣妹
They asked for the hot blonde.
男人都是色情狂
Hmm. Men are pigs.
除了金发辣妹 他们还叫我什么了
Did they call me anything else?
所以 谢谢城里的所有变态
So, thanks to all the perverts in town,
我发现我的青春年华还剩好几年呢
I realized I still have a few good years ahead of me.
如果我们为此要感谢谁的话
And if we have one person to thank for that,
那肯定是我了
It would be me.
少来
No.
演出和我想的一样烂吗
Was it as awful as I think?
收下这花儿吧
Take the flowers.
让你在我像个傻子一样出尽洋相的时候
It must have been really hard for you to be supportive
还那么支持我一定很难
while I made a fool out of myself.
来抱抱吧
Oh, come here.
卢克 你能不能安静点儿
Luke, do you mind?
我们正浓情蜜意呢
We're trying to have a moment here.
我的眼睛都能感觉到心跳了
I can feel my heartbeat in my eyes.
-他的眼睛 -没错
- In his eyes? - Yes.
我们去找工人
Okay. We'll get a janitor.
好
Okay.